ehr.com 2009-01-05

# Watson Wyatt Global - Our Firm | Privacy Policy

Watson Wyatt & Company and its majority owned subsidiaries (“Watson Wyatt”, “we”, “our”, “us”) is committed to protecting the privacy of the users (“you”, “your”) of this site (“Web Site”). We collect personally identifiable information about you only with your permission. 

**Collection of personal information** : In some cases, such as to participate in surveys, apply for employment or to contact us through our Web Site, we ask you for personal information. The information collected is related to the purpose, and includes your name, contact information, and (if applying for employment), relevant information about your qualifications.

**Security** : We will use appropriate, commercially reasonable safeguards to maintain the confidentiality of your personal information. We will take appropriate technical and organizational measures to protect your personal information against (a) accidental or unlawful destruction, (b) accidental loss and (c) unauthorized alteration, disclosure or access. Any data we collect may be transferred internationally throughout Watson Wyatt for the purposes for which it was collected. 

**Customization** : Some areas of the Web Site can be customized according to user preferences. We use individual preferences to deliver custom content online and analyze aggregate preferences in order to improve site quality. 

**Publication orders** : If a user orders a publication, their personal information will be used to fulfil the order, and may be shared with third parties involved in fulfilling the order (a printer, for instance). 

**Event registration** : If a user registers for an event online, their personal information will be used to fulfil that request, and may be shared with third parties involved with the event (a hotel, for instance). 

**Online job applications** : separate notices and policies are provided to prospective job applicants relating the use and processing of job applicant data. 

**E-mail** : If you send an e-mail message to us, we will use your e-mail address and other information you provide to respond to your request.

**Subscriptions** : If you subscribe to one of our online publications, we use the information you provide to send you e-mail updates. You can unsubscribe at any time by contacting our Webmaster whose details are provided below. 

**Surveys** : The information we collect in online surveys is used for internal research purposes. In general, we do not divulge individual responses to surveys except for participant names. Exceptions to this policy are noted when users access particular surveys. On occasions, we may share responses with a cosponsor who works with us to analyze the data; in this case, we expect the cosponsor to maintain the same level of confidentiality and security as employed by Watson Wyatt Worldwide. 

**Cookies**. A cookie is a text-only string of information stored on a user's hard drive that allows a Web Site to remember them. For general users of the site, cookies are used only during a user session (to maintain a shopping cart, for instance) and are then deleted. We do use persistent cookies to identify users who take advantage of the customization features of the site and to save this identification between site visits. 

**Third parties**. We do not sell or share personal information with third parties for their own separate use. Rather, data may be shared with third parties retained by Watson Wyatt for purposes of fulfilling their obligations to Watson Wyatt only.

**Accessing and Updating** : If your personal information changes or if you no longer wish to receive a service, please let the Webmaster know by e-mailing webmaster@watsonwyatt.com and we will correct, update or remove your details. You are entitled to see the information held about you. If you wish to do this, please contact us. 

**Modification** : This privacy policy is subject to change. All changes will be posted on this Web Site and shall apply to information provided on or after the date of posting. 

If you have any questions about Watson Wyatt's privacy practices, please contact our Webmaster at:

901 North Glebe Road   
Arlington, Virginia 22203   
e-mail: [webmaster@watsonwyatt.com](mailto:webmaster@watsonwyatt.com)
